<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bot Flow Build on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>/040-botflowbuild.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bot Flow Build on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/040-botflowbuild/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ask Actions</title>
      <link>/040-botflowbuild/10_first.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040-botflowbuild/10_first.html</guid>
      <description>Adding Ask Actions  Now that we have the NLU model, we need to use it in the flow It will look like this now Ask for Intent is used to ask the user for input  Add All Intents Ask for Slot Ask for Slot Properties </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow &amp; Data Blocks</title>
      <link>/040-botflowbuild/20_second.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040-botflowbuild/20_second.html</guid>
      <description>Flow and Data Blocks Flow Blocks   Clear Slot is useful for setting the value again. For example, capturing a password for reset, you can use the same Password Slot more than once. Can also be useful to remove private data that you do not want in subsequent flows. The only input is the Slot name
  Set Intent can be used to hard code an Intent based on a decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communicate</title>
      <link>/040-botflowbuild/30_third.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040-botflowbuild/30_third.html</guid>
      <description>Communicate   Used to add prompts that are not related to Intents or Slots
  Can be used to provide additional instructions, legal disclaimers, waiting messages or other fixed text
  Uses the Communication Sequence Builder, so allows you to prompt information from variables, such as slot values or the result of a Data Action
    The Communication Sequence Builder can also be used to change the voice of the bot dependant on language and channel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loops</title>
      <link>/040-botflowbuild/40_fourth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040-botflowbuild/40_fourth.html</guid>
      <description>Loops   Loops are useful to allow for some behaviour to be repeated and create a sequence of events that can be reused
  The standard Loops all work as they do in other flows
 Loop - Start a loop with a counter Loop Until - Loop until a condition occurs Exit Loop - Break out of a normal loop at a certain activity Next Loop - Move to the next interation(loop count) based on a cindition    They are useful to get a Slot, validate it with a Data Actionand then ask for the value again if it is not correct</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Handling</title>
      <link>/040-botflowbuild/50_fifth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040-botflowbuild/50_fifth.html</guid>
      <description>Event Handling Disconnect   There are 2 blocks in the Disconnect menu. Both indicate that the bot is done
  Exit Bot Flow is the default added to the flow and will end the Bot Flow. However, it does not end the interaction, this will return to the calling Architect flow (Inbound Call, Inbound Chat or Inbound Message) instead. Use when you are done with the bot, but want to still route to agent or call a new Bot Flow</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
